http://www.stuntdubl.com/privacy-policy/

Search
…or search All SEO Sites, thanks Lee!
Your email has been sent! Thank you!
Please enter your name, a message and a valid email address.
Your email failed. Try again later.
StuntDubl
Privacy Policy
Switch Reading StyleNighttimeDaytime
We are not affiliated or liable for the actions or claims to the companies or sites listed in our Links.
Privacy Policy:
1. Purpose
This site has adopted this Privacy Statement in order to inform you of its policies with respect to information collected from this website. Your use of this website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Statement and your consent to the practices it describes.
2. Automatic Collection of Anonymous Information
When you visit This site website, like when you visit most other websites, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged, which may include information about the type of browser you use, the server name and IP address through which you access the internet (such as “aol.com” or “earthlink.net”), the date and time you access the site, the pages you access while at This site ’s website, and the internet address of the website, if any, from which you linked directly to This site ’s site. This information is not personally identifiable.
3. Personally Identifiable Information
Personally Identifiable Information is any information that concerns you individually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name, address, telephone number, email address or any information you submitted to This site that identifies you individually.
This site will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it. Therefore, if you do not want This site to obtain any personally identifiable information about you, do not submit it.
You can visit and browse This site ’s website without revealing personally identifiable information about yourself. You may also choose to disclose personally identifiable information about yourself, which may be maintained as described below. This site may collect personally identifiable information about you from its website by methods such as the following:
4. Registration Forms
If you are offered the opportunity to enter a promotion or to become a registered user of This site ‘s website, you must apply by filling out the registration form on the site. This form requires certain personally identifiable information that may include, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and/or a unique individual password.
5. Transactions and Activity
If you become a registered user or if you conduct transactions through This site ’s website, it collects information about the transactions you engage in while on the website and your other activity on the site. This information may include, without limitation, areas of the website that you visit, transaction type, content that you view, download or submit, transaction amount and payment information.
6. Email and other voluntary communications
You may also choose to communicate with This site through email, via our website, by telephone, in writing, or through other means. We collect the information in these communications, and such information may be personally identifiable.
7. Information Use
This site may use the personally identifiable information collected through its website primarily for such purposes as:
a) helping to establish and verify the identity of users;
b) opening, maintaining, administering and servicing users’ accounts or memberships;
c) processing, servicing or enforcing transactions and sending related communications;
d) providing services and support to users;
e) improving the website, including tailoring it to users’ preferences;
f) providing users with service updates, promotional notices and offers, and other information about This site ;
g) responding to your questions inquiries, comments and instructions;
h) maintaining the security and integrity of its systems.
This site uses the anonymous browsing information collected automatically by its servers primarily to help it administer and improve its website. This site may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about its website to potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. Again, this information is not personally identifiable.
8. Disclosure of Information
This site does not provide personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their use in marketing directly to you. This site may use unaffiliated companies to help it maintain and operate its website or for other reasons related to the operation of its business, and those companies may receive your personally identifiable information for that purpose. This site may also disclose personally identifiable information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law. Finally, as This site ’s business develops, it may sell or buy corporate assets, and in such transactions customer information may be one of the transferred business assets. If This site , its internet businesses, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired, customer information may be one of the assets transferred.
9. “Cookies” and Advertisers
This site website’s server, or the servers of companies that are used to operate this site, may place a “cookie” on your computer in order to allow you to use the website and to personalize your experience.
A “cookie” is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow This site to recognize your computer while you are on its website and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies may also be used to improve the functionality of the website.
The advertisers and/or other content providers that may appear on this website may also use cookies that are not sent by This site ’s website. Such ads or content may contain cookies that help track and target the interests of users of this website in order to present “personalized” advertisements or other messages that the user might find interesting. This site is not responsible for any such cookies.
Most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of this website.
10. Security
This site maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard personally identifiable information. If transactions are offered on the site, transaction information is transmitted to and from This site in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. This site restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.
11. Choice/Opt-Out
In order to provide service to you, This site will send you communications related to your transactions, security or the administration of its website. From time to time, This site may also wish to send you updates about This site or promotions. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction/security related communications from This site , please send an email containing your request to admin<at>This site
12. Data Quality/Access
This site allows you to change, update, or delete the information you may provide in your optional registration form. If you would like to change, update, or delete your personal information, please send an email containing your request to admin<at>This site
13. Changes to this Privacy Policy
This site reserves the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, This site will post a link to the new policy on its website. In the event case of any conflict between the terms of this policy and the terms of any electronic or machine readable privacy policy (for example, a P3P electronic privacy policy), the terms of this written policy shall control.
14. Contacting Us
If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or the information practices of This site , please contact us by email at admin<at>This site
15. Governing law.
This policy and the use of this Site are governed by California law. Any claim related to the Site or this policy shall be brought in a federal or state court in California, within one year after the claim arises. You agree no such claim may be brought as a class action. Users of This site consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such court as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this policy. This site is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. If you are located outside the United States, please note the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. You hereby consent to this transfer.
16. Children.
This site does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe This site has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at admin<at>This site
17. Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements.
This site expects its partners, advertisers and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a This site page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through This site you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, advertisements, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. This site is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.
Terms of Use:
No material from this Site may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any manner or form without explicit consent from This site . Under no circumstances, including, but not limited to, negligence, shall This site be liable for any special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, the materials in this Site. You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless This site , its officers, directors, employees, and agents from and against any claims, actions, or demands, including without limitation reasonable legal and accounting fees, arising from your use of the materials or your breach of the terms of this Agreement.
Advertisers may engage in the collection of non-personally identifiable information about end users by third parties through the use of cookies and pixel tags.
End users may opt out of behavioral targeting through the opt-out link located at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
This site is participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.
His presentations are always sought after, most listened to, and highly anticipated...
Norelyn T. Babiera, President, Fiera De Manila Inc.
Todd is Mr. Online Marketing in my book..he's a one man powerhouse of web knowledge...
Jim Boykin, CEO of Internet Marketing Ninjas
Todd introduced us to the science of SEO. It was not a mistake…
Mike Stackhouse, CEO, SAMSA, Inc.
There are few people in the world who know Search Engine Optimization like Todd...
Avinash Kaushik, Evangelist, Google
Very few people can analyze a business on the web as efficiently and adroitly as Todd…
Rand Fishkin, CEO SEOMoz, Inc.
If I was to make a short list of people to go into business with Todd would make…
Jeremy Schoemaker, Shoemoney.com
…implementing a few of his ideas helped us achieve higher rankings and more sales…
Greg Hartnett, Founder, Best of the Web
I consider Todd one of the top 5 experts in the domain of internet marketing...
Kristopher Jones, CEO & Founder, Pepperjam
Todd has a great reputation in the SEO/SEM industry, and for good reason...
